《鬼娃回魂2》
早上好 沙利文先生
Good morning, Mr. Sullivan.
我一会有个会要开
I have a meeting in a few minutes
去和那些神经紧张的股东们会面
with some very jittery stockholders, Mattson.
希望你有好消息告诉我
I hope you have good news for me.
是的 先生 我会的
Yes, sir. I do, sir.
每个小报头条都刊登了
Every supermarket tabloid in the country
关于安迪·巴克利和他的杀手"好家伙"玩偶的故事
is running headlines about Andy Barclay and his killer Good Guy doll.
他妈妈和警方怎么看待这事
What about his mother and the police that were on the case?
警方很聪明 他们否认这一切
The police were smart. They denied everything,
这对我们没有什么坏处
which is fine because now they can't hurt us.
但安迪的妈妈却全然不同
But the mother's a different matter.
她在法庭上支持了儿子的说法
She backed up her boy's story in court,
所以她现在在接受精神观察
so now she's under psychiatric observation.
我的天 那孩子现在在哪
Jesus. Where's the boy now?
市中区儿童危机中心 受监护人照顾
Midtown Children's Crisis Center. Foster custody is pending.
我听了胃疼 马特森 这就是你说的好消息
My stomach hurts, Mattson. Is this what you call good news?
是 不 我正要说呢 先生
Yes... No. I'm getting to that, sir.
我们最大的问题在于那些谣言
Our biggest problem has been the rumors. A lot...
早上好 沙利文先生
Good morning, Mr. Sullivan.
大家都在开公司的玩笑
A lot of people are saying that some joker here at the company
他们还模仿玩偶的发声
must have tampered with the doll's voice cassette, you know?
"嗨 我叫恰吉 我是湖边的杀手"
"Hi. I'm Chucky. I'm the Lakeshore Strangler.
"现在我就要杀了你"有些就像
"And now I'm gonna kill you." Something like...
就像这个样子
Well, something like that.
但是 也有好消息 沙利文先生
But the good news, Mr. Sullivan,
我们找到了那个玩偶
is that now we've got the doll.
已经从头到脚地重塑了
We've rebuilt it from head to toe.
它已经大面积被烧毁了
A lot of it was burned to a crisp,
不过所有部件都检查过了 发声磁带 伺服系统
but everything checks out, the voice cassettes, the servomechanisms.
我们没有发现任何问题
We've found absolutely nothing.
这是一份质量认证报告
This is a quality control report.
我敢说那些股东看了会很开心
I'm sure it will make the stockholders very happy.
我要亲自看下那个玩偶
I want to see the doll for myself.
没问题
Absolutely.
伙计们 沙利文先生来了 准备好了吗
Gentlemen, Mr. Sullivan's here. We ready?
稍等一下 我们不太习惯人工操作
Well, give us a minute. We're not used to making them manually.
- 出什么问题了 - 不知道 卡住了
- What's wrong? - I don't know. It's stuck.
只是
Just...
他们会搞定的
They'll have this worked out.
我的天啊
My God!
噢 天啊
Oh, Jesus!
安迪 你还在梦到恰吉吗
Andy, you still dreaming about Chucky?
有时会
Sometimes.
- 想谈谈它吗 - 不
- You want to talk about it? - No.
来吧 安迪 还记得我和你说的吗
Come on, Andy. Remember what I told you?
把问题说出来就可以
Talking helps make
- 把梦魇赶走 - 把梦魇赶走
- the nightmares go away. - The nightmares go away.
恰吉想控制我的灵魂
Well, Chucky was trying to take over my soul.
为什么
Why?
他是个坏人 他进入了我的"好家伙"玩偶里
He was this bad man who got inside my Good Guy doll,
所以他才没有死去
so he wouldn't have to go to hell.
但是后来他想进入我的体内
But then he wanted to get inside me.
为什么 安迪
Why, Andy?
因为如果他呆在玩偶里的时间太长 他就出不来了
'Cause if he stayed inside the doll too long, he'd be trapped in there.
他需要我是因为 我是第一个知道秘密的人
He needed me 'cause I was the first person he told his secret to.
什么秘密
What secret?
他的真名叫查尔斯·李·雷
That his real name was Charles Lee Ray.
孩子 这只是个可怕的梦
Boy, that's a scary dream.
这是真的
It was.
梦里的东西不会伤害你
Dreams can't hurt you.
因为梦是假的
Dreams aren't real.
- 对不对 - 对
- Right? - Right.
在哪
In here?
那边
In there.
赶快
Let's hurry up.
马森特 我不关心这些 不要把这事传开
Mattson, I don't care what it takes. Put a lid on this.
是 先生 这没问题 我会保密的
Yes, sir. That's not a problem. I'll take care of this.
听我说
Listen to me.
要么摆平 要么24小时内自己走人 明白
You smother this or you're out of here in 24 hours. You got that?
是
Yes, sir.
现在 别打扰我了 我要去开会 必须走了
Now, if you will excuse me, I've got a meeting I've got to get to.
只要股东和我都可以赚到钱
As far as the stockholders and I are concerned,
这件事就算结了
this matter is finished.
是
Yes, sir.
您想让我怎么处理这些玩偶
What do you want me to do with the doll?
塞你屁眼里吧
Stick it up your ass.
事实上 那几起谋杀事件让他精神受到严重创伤
Naturally, he was badly traumatized by the murders,
好在他这个年龄很容易康复
but they bounce back pretty fast at that age.
可怜的孩子
Poor kid.
安迪现在需要的是一个正常的家庭 一个新的开始
What Andy needs now is a normal family environment, a fresh start
和一个忘掉过去不愉快的机会
and a chance to forget the past.
你们把很多孩子照顾得那么好
Since you two have done so well with so many kids,
在他妈妈康复之前 希望他能得到你们的照顾
we were hoping you might foster him until his mother recovers.
- 正好我们可以多照顾一个 - 呃
- There's always room for one more. - Mmm.
你那是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
呃 是这样的
Uh, well...
他看起来很正常 这些是怎样影响了他
He seems normal enough, but how has all this affected him?
为了接受一些
Well, in order to come to terms with
令他难以理解的事情
something he couldn't possibly understand,
他把那些想象成了童话一般的故事
he turned it all into a kind of fairy tale.
他竟然坚持说是他的玩偶杀了人
He insisted his doll was responsible.
说什么玩偶被查尔斯·李·雷的灵魂控制了
He said it was possessed by the soul of Charles Lee Ray.
谁
Who?
那个湖边的杀人犯
The Lakeshore Strangler.
他杀了很多人 以一种巫毒教的杀人仪式
He murdered a dozen people in this series of ritual voodoo killings.
我们真有能力去照顾这样一个孩子吗
Are we even qualified to take care of a boy like this?
我明白你的担虑 辛普森先生
Well, I understand your concern, Mr. Simpson,
但我敢肯定 他只是在用一种孩子
but I'm sure you can see that this is just a child's way
处理问题的方式而已
of coping with a difficult situation.
安迪现在已经没事了
Andy's fine now.
他只是想好好的生活
He just wants to get on with his life.
安迪 你想吃什么
So, Andy, what do you like to eat?
什么都可以
All kinds of things.
那么 你最喜欢吃什么呢
Well, what's your very favorite food in the whole wide world?
巧克力
Chocolate.
除了巧克力呢
Besides chocolate.
我妈妈早餐经常给我准备鸡蛋 我喜欢鸡蛋
Mmm... My mom used to fix me eggs for breakfast. I like eggs.
好 我们就停到那家店旁边
You got it. We should stop at the store.
- 前面那家 - 没错 就那家有机食品店
- The one down here? - Yeah, the organic one.
你有口福了 安迪 乔安妮的厨艺超级棒
You're in luck, Andy. Joanne's a terrific cook.
你喜欢吃寿司吗 你知道我说的是
You like sushi? You know what I mean by...
菲尔 小心
Phil, look out!
天啊
Jesus Christ!
当心有车
Look out for the car.
嘿 等等我
Hey, wait up.
安迪 就当在自己家
Make yourself comfortable, Andy.
谢谢
Thanks.
我下午得回办公室一趟
Well, I have to get back to the office this afternoon.
我以为你都处理好了呢
I thought that you'd done everything.
啊 啊
Ah-ah-ah...
第一条规定 不要动这些古董
First rule. Don't touch the old stuff.
抱歉
Sorry.
没事 还好 没犯什么错
Well, that's okay. No foul.
只是 我们收集的这些
It's just that we collect this junk,
古董都很容易碎
and a lot of it's kind of fragile.
- 你喜欢它 - 恩啊
- You like it? - Uh-huh.
它在我家已经传了三代了
It's been in my family for three generations.
我外婆传给我母亲 母亲又传给了我
My grandmother gave it to my mother, and my mother gave it to me.
那你是要传给谁呢
And who are you gonna give it to?
你先把行李提到楼上 顺便参观下
Why don't you take this upstairs and explore?
我一会就过去
I'll be up there in a minute.
好
Okay.
你怎么想的
What do you think?
我还要适应他一段时间
I'll get used to him.
老天 你知道敲门不
Jesus. Did you ever hear of knocking?
安迪 你有没有找到
Andy, did you find...
你疯了吗 把它给我
What, are you crazy? Give them to me.
行了 乔安妮
Come on, Joanne.
如果被菲尔看到 他会杀了你
Phil will shoot you if he catches you again.
安迪 这是凯尔 她也和我们住一块
Andy, this is Kyle. She's staying with us, too.
幸会
Charmed.
凯尔 这是什么
Kyle, what is this?
你都来三个星期了 行李怎么还没打开
You've been here three weeks. Why haven't you unpacked?
开那干嘛 我就没在一个家里呆够过一月
What for? I've never spent more than a month in any home.
就冲这态度 我就知道原因了
With that attitude, I can see why.
快 把这些收走
Come on. Put these things away,
然后 过来帮我
and then would you do me a favor
准备晚餐 好吗
and help me get dinner started?
不行 今晚要去打工
Can't. Got to work tonight.
凯尔 已经连续三晚了
Kyle, that's the third night in a row.
我真心希望你能花点时间陪陪家里的人
I'd really like it if you'd spend a little time with the family.
我需要钱 明年我就靠自己了
I need the money. I'm gonna be on my own next year.
没错 但在那之前 你还有我们 不是吗
Yes, well, until then, you're with us, okay?
- 我们走 安迪 - 拜拜
- Come along, Andy. - Bye.
在这我想你会开心的
I think you'll be very happy here.
这就是你的房间
This is your room, right here.
我专门给你做了这窗帘
I made those curtains just for you.
我猜你喜欢蓝色
I bet blue is your favorite color.
随便看看吧 我去把行李收好
Take a look around. I'll start to unpack.
哇哦
Wow!
我猜你喜欢的 嗯 柜子里还有呢
I thought you might like those. Um... There's more in the closet.
晚饭前 我们先参观下后院
Before dinner, we'll go explore the backyard.
晚点 我再讲故事给你听
And, later, I'll read you some stories.
你喜欢吗
Would you like that?
邻居有很多像你这么大的小朋友
There are lots of kids your age in the neighborhood, Andy.
我相信你会认识很多新朋友的
I'm sure you're going to make all sorts of new friends.
嘿嘿
Hey,hey!
安迪 第二条规定 不许在房间里奔跑
Andy, rule number two, no running in the house.
那只是个玩偶 你在听我说吗
It's only a doll. Andy, are you listening to me?
噢 对不起 安迪 我没看到它在那
Oh, Andy, I'm so sorry. I didn't realize that was in there.
我们这有很多孩子 很难搞清所有东西在哪
We've had so many kids here, it's hard to keep track of everything.
我去把它丢掉
I'll get rid of it.
嗨 我叫汤米 我会是你永远的朋友
Hi, I'm Tommy. And I'm your friend till the end.
我们先住进来 然后去吃晚饭 好吗
Why don't we get settled in, and then we'll have some dinner, okay?
妈的
Shit.
嗨 加布里埃拉 猜猜我谁
Hello, Gabriella. Guess who?
没错是我
That's right.
伏特加 我当然记得伏特加了
The vodka? The vodka. Of course I remembered the vodka.
长达两周的周年庆 我怎么会把它忘了呢
Two-week anniversary. You think I'd forget the vodka?
我知道它对你来说很重要
I know what that does to you.
没问题 等我吧
Okay, well, wait for me.
我在路上
On my way. Yeah.
妈的
Shit.
我想玩"红灯"
I want to play Red Light.
不行 萨米 我现在不想玩什么"红灯"
No, Sammy, I don't want to play Red Light now.
你应该马上回去睡觉
I want you to go back to bed right now.
我害怕
But I'm scared.
没什么可怕的 只是暴风雨而已
There's nothing to be scared of. It's just a storm.
克雷斯·普尔
Grace Poole.
我想找安迪·巴克利
Yes, I'm trying to reach Andy Barclay.
安迪已经不住这了 你是谁
Andy no longer lives here. Who is this?
我是他的叔叔 查尔斯
This is his Uncle Charles.
不好意思 只收现金
Sorry, cash only.
可这是金卡啊 和现金一样用
But that's a gold card. That's just as good as cash.
这儿不行 我们不刷信用卡
Not here, it ain't. We don't accept credit cards.
可我没带现金啊
I don't carry cash, okay?
不许动
Don't move!
我的天啊
Jesus!
天啊 你想要什么
God. Okay. Okay, what do you want?
- 别多问 开你的车 - 好 好
- No questions. Just drive. - Okay, okay.
继续往前
Keep going.
就这 停车
Now, park this piece of shit.
把手背在座子后面
Put your arms behind the seat.
- 你想做什么 - 照做
- What? - Do it!
好 好 冷静 冷静 别开枪
Okay. Take it easy. Take it easy. Please, don't shoot.
我没带现金 我只有张金卡
Look, I don't carry cash. I got a gold card.
你要什么我都给你
I'll give you anything you want. Tell me what you want.
他妈的 别乱动
Freeze, asshole.
车 车归你了
Take my... Take the car.
把我扔下车就行 求你放过我吧
And you can drop me off, but just, please, leave me alone.
求你了
Please.
你死了
Bang. You're dead.
不 不 不
No! No! No!
别 别
No!No!No!
"伐木工跟他妻子争吵了很久"
"The woodcutter argued for a long time with his wife,
"但她生起气来会变得很可怕"
"but she was such a horrid, frightening woman when she was angry,
"最后 他只好同意了她的计划"
"that in the end he agreed to her plan.
"早上 继母过来叫他们"
"In the morning, their stepmother called them.
她说"我们一起去森林吧"
"I think it would be nice if we all went into the forest today," she said.
"韩赛尔与格蕾特并没有答复"
"Hansel and Gretel did not reply,
"只是跟着父母进入了丛林深处"
"but followed their parents into the dark forest."
从此 他们过着快乐的生活
Where they all lived happily ever after.
- 不 他们没有 - 现在 他们有
- No, they don't. - Well, they do for now.
明晚 我们再继续讲
We'll finish it tomorrow night.
别走
Don't go.
有什么事儿
What's the matter?
我想妈妈了
I miss my mother.
噢 我知道你想
Oh, honey, I know you do.
我还能见到妈妈吗
Will I ever see her again?
当然能 我保证
Of course you will. I promise.
别担心 我会陪着你的
Don't worry. I'll stay with you as long as you want.
妈妈经常唱歌给我听 你能唱给我听吗
My mother used to sing to me. Will you sing to me?
妈的
Shit.
嗨 我是汤米
Hi. I'm Tommy.
闭嘴 白痴
Shut up, you idiot.
我喜欢被拥抱 我喜欢被拥抱
I like to be hugged. I like to be hugged. I like to be hugged.
我喜欢被拥抱
I like to be hugged...
抱你个头
Hug this.
我喜欢被拥抱 我喜欢被拥抱
I like to be hugged. I like to be hugged. I like...
- 什么声音 - 没什么 乖乖睡吧
- What was that? - Nothing. Now, go to sleep.
没人会伤害你的
Nobody's going to hurt you.
汤米 吃屎去吧
Eat dirt, Tommy.
你们谁想说说这事
Do either of you have anything to say about this?
我觉得应该先找律师谈谈
I think we should talk to a lawyer first.
凯尔 别开玩笑了 那雕像对我很重要
Kyle, that's not funny. That statue was very important to me.
你们中有一个该向乔安妮道歉
I think one of you owes Joanne an apology.
不关我的事
I'm innocent.
安迪
Andy?
不是我做的
I didn't do it.
好吧 我没得选择了
All right. You leave me no choice.
在有人坦白前 谁都别离开这
Until somebody fesses up, you're both grounded.
我今晚有约
But I have a date tonight.
那对不起了
Sorry.
真该感谢你给了我一个放假的机会
This is exactly how I wanted to spend my day off. Thanks a lot.
可我真的没有打碎那个雕像
But I didn't break the statue. Really.
好吧 也许它是自己掉下去的
Yeah. Maybe it just fell?
嘿 你想让我背对着你说话吗
Hey. You want to hear me say your name backwards?
凯尔
Kyle.
拿着
Hold this.
天啊 把它给我
Jesus. Give me that.
你他妈到底想干什么
What the hell do you think you're doing?
我就是想尝尝什么味儿
I wanted to taste it.
说实话 就是狗屎味
Get real. It tastes like shit, okay?
这些东西对你没好处
These things are very bad for you.
那你为什么还吸呢
Then why do you do it?
因为只有大人才可以做那些对他们有害的事
Because grown-ups are allowed to do things that are bad for them.
可你也不是大人
You're not a grown-up.
安迪 你让我感到头疼了
You're beginning to get on my nerves, Andy.
你过来帮我吧
Now, why don't you give me a hand over here?
辛普森先生脾气不太好啊
Mr. Simpson is kind of grouchy, isn't he?
这还不算糟
He's not so bad.
要换做我以前待过的那家 你要是斜着眼看他们
I've had fosters that would shoot you
非杀了你不可
for staring at them cross-eyed.
是真的
Really?
当然是真的了
Sure.
毕竟又不是他们亲生的 不过是领养的而已
They figure you're not theirs. You're just passing through.
只要你一犯错
The minute you screw up...
就会严厉地惩罚你
Argh! They let you have it.
这件事让我很不高兴
I got to tell you, I'm not happy with this whole thing.
再考虑考虑吧
Having second thoughts?
你得承认 他是个麻烦的孩子吧
Well, you have to admit, he's a very troubled little boy,
而且 他明显还没有忘记那个玩偶事件
and he obviously has not come to terms with this whole doll thing.
他可能需要多一点照顾
Look, all I'm saying is that he may need
可我们给不了他
more attention than we can give him.
菲尔 安迪有过可怕的经历
Phil, Andy's been through hell.
你得多给他些时间 他会好起来的
You have to give him some time. He'll settle down.
而且 我挺喜好他
Besides, I like him.
我讨厌你
I hate you.
嗨 我是 汤米 我是你永远的朋友
Hi. I'm...Tommy, and I'm your friend to the end.
啊 哦
Hi-de-ho.
嗨
Hi.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
凯尔 你想你的爸爸妈妈吗
Kyle, do you miss your mom and dad?
你不会去想从来不认识的人的
You can't miss someone you never knew.
他们在哪
Where are they?
我不知道
I have no idea.
我还没出生 我爸爸就死了
My dad left before I was born.
在我三岁的时候 我妈把我送给别人抚养
My mom put me up for adoption when I was three.
你还记得她吗
Do you remember her?
我试着去忘了她
I made it a point to forget.
这样会好受点
It's easier that way.
嘿 休息时间到了
Hey. Break time.
下来吧
Move over.
要我推吗
Want a push?
不用了
No, thank you.
来吧 很好玩的
Come on. It's fun.
安迪 我就是想坐下来休息会
Come on, Andy, please, I just want to sit here, okay?
说晚了 起来了
Too late. There you go.
安迪 让我休息会 停
Andy, come on. Give me a break. Stop it.
不行
No.
安迪 我要杀了你
Andy, I'll kill you.
让我下去
Come on. Let me off.
安迪
Andy!
我会抓住你的
I'll get you.
- 安迪 放开 - 吃晚饭了
- Come on, Andy, cut it out. - Dinner!
哇哦
Whoa!
啊
Aah!
来 我们比赛跑步
Mayhem. Come on. I'll race you.
这不公平 你抢跑了
Not fair. You got a head start.
别忘了你的玩偶
Excuses,excuses. Don't forget your doll.
凯尔呢 她会喜好吗
For Kyle. Think she'll like it?
我怎么会知道女孩子喜欢什么
What do I know about teenage girls?
肯定比三周前更了解了吧
More than you did three weeks ago.
我可不敢肯定
I'm not so sure.
我在想要给安迪什么呢
I was thinking we should get something for Andy.
让他觉得已经安定下来了
Make him feel more settled.
有什么想法吗
Any ideas?
安定剂怎么样
Yeah. How about a Valium?
吃惊吗
Surprise.
想我了吗 安迪 我可是很想你啊
Did you miss me, Andy? I sure missed you.
我告诉过你
I told you.
我们会是永远的朋友
We were going to be friends to the end.
现在又到玩的时间了
And now it's time to play.
我想到一个新游戏 老朋友
I got a new game, sport.
它叫做"灵魂隐匿"
It's called Hide the Soul.
你猜怎么玩 你是主角
And guess what? You're it.
[咒语]
我祈求你 赐予我力量吧
Give me the power, I beg...
这事还没完 小鬼
This isn't over, you little shit.
我可不想在这该死的橡胶玩具里度过余生
I'm not gonna spend the rest of my life as a plastic freak.
下次你一个人的时候 你就是我的了
Next time you're alone, you're mine.
噢 天啊
Oh, my God.
是恰吉 看啊
It's Chucky. Look out!
闭嘴吧 你会把菲尔和乔安妮吵醒的
Shut up. You'll wake Phil and Joanne.
杀了他 杀了他
Kill him! Kill him!
安迪 够了
Andy, stop it, will you?
发生什么事了
What the hell is this, now?
是恰吉 他找到我了 他想要控制我的灵魂
It's Chucky. I told you he'd find me. He tried to take over my soul.
安迪 冷静下来
Andy, calm down.
你不用起来的
You didn't have to wait up.
是吗 凯尔 我可不相信你
Yeah? You know, Kyle, I don't believe you.
你把安迪绑起来 让他不能说你坏话
You actually tied this child up, so he wouldn't tell on you.
- 对不对 - 别说了 菲尔
- Is that it? - Come on, Phil.
- 是恰吉干的 - 可以了啊
- Chucky did it. - That's enough now.
恰吉 我知道了
Chucky? I've had it.
你得把他杀了
But you've got to kill him.
安迪
Andy!
请听我说 我没有骗你
Please, listen to me. I'm not lying.
如果不杀他 他还会来找我
If you don't kill him, he'll come get me.
安迪 冷静一下
Andy, calm down.
我去把他丢掉
I'm going to get rid of it.
看到没 丢掉了 他再也不会伤害到你了
There, see? He's gone. He can't bother you anymore.
不
No.
我还能变回人类吗
I'm turning human again?
如果还不赶快离开这个身体 就坏事了
If I don't get out of this body soon, I'm screwed.
快点 安迪 我们要迟到了
Come on, Andy. We're late.
安迪 你的午餐
Andy. Don't forget your lunch.
鸡蛋沙拉
Egg salad.
不管你做什么 别那么紧张 好吗
Now, whatever you do, don't act nervous, okay?
不然没人和你玩 要表现得像他们亲生的一样
They'll smell a new kid a mile off. Just act like you belong.
你找什么呢
What are you looking for?
没 没什么
Nothing.
是不是恰吉来找你了
Is it Chucky coming to get you?
安迪 你昨晚把自己绑起来 是怎么做到的
Andy, how did you manage to tie yourself up like that last night?
我早就告诉过你了
I already told you.
说实话
Get real.
你和他们一样 都不相信我
You're just like everybody else. You don't believe me either.
- 凯尔 - 嗨 亚当
- Kyle? - Hey, Adam. Hi.
昨晚怎么走那么早 你错过了很多有趣的事
Why'd you have to leave so early last night? You missed all the fun.
唉 我真悲剧
Story of my life.
快点来吧
Come on now.
在哪呢
Where is it?
哈哈
Ah-ha!
"皮诺曹高兴地跳起来 大喊 我活了 我活了"
"Pinocchio jumped for joy, shouting, I'm alive! I'm alive!"
"那只会说话的蟋蟀说"他会说什么呢
"Then the talking cricket said..." What'd he say?
"如果你表现得足够好 并且保证不说谎话"
"If you're very, very good, and promise to tell no lies,
"你就会变成一个真正的有生命的小孩"
"then you will become a real, live boy."
"而那些反复无常的孩子"
"Boys who are bent on following their caprices
"会得到应有的报应 迟早会后悔的"
"and will have their own way, sooner or later repent."
别碰我"小薯片"
Get lost, microchip.
安迪 我惹你烦了吗
Am I boring you, Andy?
没 凯特
No, Miss...
凯特韦尔
Kettlewell.
凯特韦尔小姐
我对捣乱的学生没多少耐心
I have precious little patience for disruptive students.
他刚才敲我
But he just whacked...
尤其是新生 更应该
Especially new students, whose utmost concern
表现好一点
should be getting on my good side.
走之前把课桌摆放整齐 清理干净
I want those desks spick and span before anyone leaves.
安迪 你觉得这很好玩吗
Andy! You think this is funny?
不是我干的
I didn't do that.
下课了 别忘了明天的拼写测验
Go ahead, kids. Don't forget the spelling test tomorrow.
不是你是谁 过来 在这坐着
Not you. Come over here. Sit down and get comfy.
你在这呆着
You're going to be here for a while.
我发誓 不是我干的
But I didn't do it, I swear.
不是你 那是谁啊
No? Then who did?
别再说是玩具做的了
Don't even think about it.
没有玩具 头趴下
No toys. Head down.
趴下
Head down.
来玩捉迷藏
Peekaboo!
安迪 放我出去
Please, let me out of here, Andy.
这里很黑
It's dark in here.
我保证 我不再杀人了 好吗
I promise I won't kill anyone else. Okay?
打开这该死的门
Now, open the goddamn door.
放我出去 你这小混蛋
Let me out, you little dick.
你他妈放我出去
Let me the fuck out.
安迪 我说过呆在你座位上 离开那
Andy, I told you to stay in your seat. Come out of there.
把门打开
Open this door right now.
安迪 快点出来
Andy, come out this very second.
安迪 安迪
Andy! Andy!
安迪
Andy?
安迪 这不好玩
Andy, this isn't funny.
你好淘气啊 凯特韦尔小姐
You've been very naughty, Miss Kettlewell.
安迪 整件事是怎么样的
Andy, what's this all about?
恰吉跟踪我到学校 他还想再抓我 我就回家了
Chucky followed me to school. He tried to get me again, so I ran home.
你知道他在说什么吗
Do you know what's he talking about?
他的老师打电话过来
His teacher called,
让他放学后留堂
said she was keeping him after school for detention,
说他在纸上写些污言秽语
said he wrote an obscenity on his paper.
是恰吉写的
Chucky did it.
好了 安迪 过来
All right, Andy. Come on.
这件事就这样结束了
This is going to stop,
我不允许在我家里发生这种事
'cause I will not allow this foolishness in my house.
- 你明白吗 开门 - 菲尔
- Do you understand? Open the door. - Oh, Phil...
乔安妮 别说了
Joanne, please.
开门
Open the door.
Open it.
开门
Open it!
现在你看着那 告诉我看到了什么
Now, I want you to look down there and tell me what you see.
看到了恰吉 但
It's Chucky, but...
他叫汤米
His name is Tommy,
他从昨晚就在那了
and he's been there since last night, hasn't he?
是不是
Hasn't he?
别伤心了 乔安妮 这孩子需要专业的帮助
For crying out loud, Joanne, the child needs professional help.
你就别假装在关心他了
Stop pretending you're worried about Andy.
你从一开始就不想他住在这
You never wanted him here in the first place.
不是这样的
That's not true.
那你想让我怎么做 把他送回去
So, what are you suggesting we do? Send him back?
你不用这么大吼大叫
You don't have to make it sound so horrible.
你知道这种创伤会带来什么吗
Do you have any idea how traumatic that would be?
创伤 谁 你还是他
Traum... For whom, Joanne, for him or for you?
如果他还住在这里 早晚会把整个家庭拆散
Look, if that kid stays here, he's gonna tear this family apart.
家庭 这就是你所谓的家庭
Family? Is this what you call a family?
家庭是不会放弃他们孩子的
Families don't just give up on their children.
乔安妮 他又不是我们的孩子
Joanne, he's not our child.
这不是世界末日
It's not the end of the world.
可他们要把我送走
But they're going to send me away.
你会没事的
You'll be okay.
我能去哪
Where will I go?
安迪
Andy.
我在很多不同的家庭待过
I've lived with dozens of different families,
当我开始习惯下来时
and they always seem to send me away
他们就想着把我送走
just when I'm getting comfortable,
- 你知道这对我有什么影响吗 - 什么
- but you know what? - What?
每次都会让我变得更加坚强
Every time it happens, it just makes me stronger,
因为这提醒着我 唯一能依靠的就是自己
because it reminds me that the only one I can count on is myself.
明白了 你从现在开始就要学习变得坚强
Okay? And you have to learn that now.
我知道这话听着不舒服
I know it sounds tough,
但是你要去面对
but you'll deal with it.
没关系的
It doesn't matter.
不管我去哪 恰吉都会找到我的
Wherever I go, Chucky will find me.
以7比6的微弱优势
...advances over the declines by a seven to six margin...
怎么了
What's wrong?
我好像听到楼下有什么动静
I thought I heard something downstairs.
是某个孩子吧
It's one of the children.
这正是我担心的
That's what I'm afraid of.
你为什么要反抗 我们马上就会更加亲密了
Why fight it, Andy? We're going to be very close.
我们很快就分不开了
In fact, we're going to be fucking inseparable.
发生了什么事
What the hell's going on down...
安迪
Andy...
把刀子放下
Put down the knife.
我需要用它来
But I need it for...
先把刀子放下 我们来谈谈
Just put the knife down, and we'll talk about it.
一切都会好起来的
Everything is going to be just fine.
倒吊起来的滋味怎么样 菲尔
How's it hanging, Phil?
噢 天啊 菲尔
No. Oh, God, Phil.
我去叫救护车
I'll call an ambulance.
菲尔 菲尔
Phil. Phil.
噢 天啊 不
Oh, God! No!
天啊
Oh, God!
从我眼前消失
Get away from me!
天啊
Oh, God!
不 我们什么也没听到
No, we didn't hear anything. Nothing.
我应该听他的话的
I should have listened to him.
如果我当初听他的 他就不会死了
He'd be here now if only I'd listened to him.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
我来拿吧
I'll take care of this.
安迪 你会没事的
Andy, you'll be fine now.
你跟我们在这呆几天吧
You come stay at the center with us for a few days
我们再给你找个新的家庭
until we can find you a new family.
我们也给凯尔找过很多个家庭了
We've placed Kyle with a number of families.
一切都会好起来的
Things always seem to work out okay.
是不啊
Don't they?
是的
Yeah.
这是你的东西
There's your stuff.
来吧 安迪 我们走
Come on, Andy. Let's go.
他还在地下室 不要被他缠上
He's still in the cellar, Kyle. Don't let him get you, too.
安迪
Andy?
我们很快就完事
We'll be out of your way in just a minute here.
除了这个男孩 还有谁看到了事故的经过
Did anyone, besides the boy, witness the accident?
- 没 - 好的
- No. - Okay.
我们走
Let's go.
乔安妮
Joanne!
Joanne?
乔安妮
Joanne!
贱货 你弄伤我了
Bitch. You hurt me.
我们还要多久才到
How much further till we get to the kid?
还要一段路程
A ways.
开快点
Step on it.
干嘛这么急啊
What's the rush?
如果我不能尽快离开这身体 就再也出不去了
If I don't get out of this body soon, I'll be trapped in here.
你看什么看
What are you looking at?
快点
Floor it.
老实说 这车只能开这么快了
Get real. This is a station wagon.
妈的
Shit!
靠边停车
Pull over.
给我注意点
Behave yourself.
我随时可以杀了你
I'll kill you if lhave to.
看一下你驾照
Okay, honey, let's see your license.
这里限速45 你开到了60 什么事这么着急
You were clocking 60 in a 45. What's your hurry?
我有个约会
I have a date.
你最好换个理由
You're going to have to do better than that.
这是个"好家伙"玩偶吧
That's one of those Good Guys, isn't it?
是的
Yes, it is.
我喜好这东西 你叫什么名字
I love these things. What's your name, buddy?
恰吉
Chucky.
太不可思议了
That's incredible.
我想说
I'll say.
那是什么
What the hell's that?
你见过会撒尿的玩偶吗
You've seen dolls that pee?
这个会流血
This one bleeds.
好吧
Okay, look,
慢一点开
just slow it down.
系上安全带
And buckle up for safety.
走吧
Now, get going.
你没事吧 宝贝
You okay, honey?
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm.
别被虫子咬了
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
快点 再快点
Come on. Step on it.
好 我们刚才又超速了
Fine. We'll just get pulled over again.
闭嘴 开你的车 不然我打碎你的牙
Just shut up and drive before I kick your fucking teeth in.
你个该死的女司机
You goddamn women drivers!
妈的
Fuck.
去你妈的 混蛋
Fucking bastard.
安迪
Shit. Andy.
娱乐时间结束了
Playtime's over.
安迪 你在干什么
Andy, what are you doing?
来 我们要离开这里
Come on. We've got to get out of the building.
凯尔 你在这干什么
Kyle, what's going on here?
是你做的
You did this, didn't you?
他做的
He did it.
来我办公室
Get into my office.
你就是这样开玩笑的
Is this your idea of a joke?
把那个给我
Give me that.
吃惊了 是吧
Amazing, isn't it?
过来
Come on!
我们来玩一个叫"恰吉说"的游戏
Okay, sport, we're going to have a little game of Chucky Says.
恰吉说"别磨蹭"
Chucky says, "Move your ass."
振作起来
Snap out of it!
你就当这里没那个死人
You act like you've never seen a dead body before.
安迪 开门
Andy, come on! Open it.
安迪 快开门
Andy! Open the door!
所有人出去
Come on! Everybody out!
进去 快
Inside. Hurry.
停下
Stop!
快
Come on.
小姐 开慢一点
Hey, lady, slow down, will you?
经过
* Passin' by *
说出你的祈祷 安迪
Say your prayers, Andy.
妈的
God damn it!
靠边
Pull over!
什么
What?
靠边
Pull over!
你当你在做什么啊
Just what in the hell do you think you're doing?
放我走 放我走
Let me go. Let me go.
你他妈有病是吧
What the fuck's wrong with you?
让我走
Let go!
死疯子
Crazy bitch!
我们到家了
We're home.
闭上眼睛 数到七
Close your eyes and count to seven.
当你醒来 就在天堂了
When you wake, you'll be in heaven.
就是这样了
This is it, world.
从此刻起
From now on,
不再有"玩偶"先生
no more Mr. Good Guy.
[咒语]
我祈求你 赐予我力量吧
Give me the power, I beg of you.
不
No!
你个小杂种
You little shit!
你知道你刚才做了什么吗
Do you know what you've done?
太迟了 我在身体里耽搁太久了
It's too late. I've spent too much time in this body.
我他妈要被困在里面了
I'm fucking trapped in here.
怎么了
What the hell?
安迪 快跑
Andy, run.
- 安迪 - 凯尔
- Andy. - Kyle.
你没事吧 来
Are you okay? Come on.
妈的
Shit!
安迪 快点
Andy, hurry up.
我们走 我在前面 跟紧我
Let's go. I'll go first. Stay right behind me.
快点
Come on.
安迪 快一点
Andy, step on it.
加把劲 把手给我
Reach! Give me your hand!
安迪 停下来 抓住边上
Andy! Stop yourself. Grab the side.
安迪 快 他就在你后面
Andy! Hurry up! He's right behind you.
你个混蛋
You bastard!
不要往后看 往前爬 快点
Don't look back. Come on. Hurry!
你逃不出我的手心
You can't get away from me!
把手伸过来
Give me your hand!
快了
Reach!
我要杀了你 安迪
I'm going to kill you, Andy!
- 回来 - 走走走 从那下去
- Come on. - Go!Go!Go! Run down there.
我会抓到你的
I'm going to get you fuckers.
天啊
God!
我的天
Oh, God!
过来 你能行
Come on. Do it!
过来 把手伸过来
Come on. Give me your hand.
不要害怕 加油
Don't be afraid. Come on.
再近一点 就能抓到我的手了
Closer. Closer so you can grab my hand.
安迪 就现在
Andy. Now!
打不开
Can't open it.
我们怎么出去
How will we get out?
我们找另一条路 把手给我
We'll have to find another way. Give me your hand.
我讨厌小孩
I hate kids.
有异常
Terrific.
躲开
Duck!
按下去
Do it!
安迪 求你了
Andy, please.
我只是跟你玩玩
I was only playing.
不要
No, please!
不不不
No!No!God!No!No!No!
噢
Holy shit.
我们做到了
We did it.
我们离开这
Let's get out of here.
- 让我看看 你没事吧 - 没事
- Let's see. Are you okay? - Yeah.
这是什么
What's this?
谢谢你来找我
Thanks for coming after me.
你欠我一次啊 小鬼
Yeah, well, you owe me one, squirt.
凯尔
Kyle!
我抓到你了 安迪
I've got you now, Andy,
你知道我该做什么了吧
and you know what I'm going to do to you?
我要砍下你的腿
I'm going to cut off your legs, too.
不
No!
凯尔 凯尔
Kyle! Kyle!
凯尔 凯尔 醒一醒
Kyle! Kyle! Kyle, wake up!
凯尔
Kyle!
走 走
Come on. Come on.
天啊 你对他做了什么
Ugh! God. What did you do to him?
好了 安迪
All right, Andy.
凯尔 凯尔
Kyle! Kyle!
吃屎去吧
Eat this, you son of a bitch.
走
Come on.
我们去哪
Where are we going?
回家
Home.
家在哪
Where's home?
我也不知道
Andy, I have no idea.